# Samantha Thick

Junior in the School of Information following the Information Analysis track with a side focus in User Experience Design. Interested in new uses for technology in order to integrate business, society, and design to make information more compatible for everyday uses.

1203 White Street Ann Arbor, MI 48104 (810) 358-8581 sthick@umich.edu

https://github.com/sthick

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Michigan** — *Information Systems*

Ann Arbor, MI -- September 2017 - May 2021

- *School of Information* Bachelor of Science in Information with a focus in Information Analysis and User Experience Design
- Major GPA: 3.7

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## University of Michigan, Softball Manager

Ann Arbor, MI -- September 2017 - Present

- Collect team performance data using Flightscope, Rapsodo, and Bats technology engaging with coaches by presenting pitching and hitting performance data for use in training and player development
- Manage practice and game set-up providing support to coaches and team members whenever necessary
- Assist in monitoring social media video and photography posts for Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook

#### Cavaliers Holdings LLC, IT Development Intern

Cleveland, OH -- June 2019 - August 2019

- Used API documentation to pull LeagueApps and Facebook Ad Data and created Python program for the Digital Media team to upload and organize team history projects
- Created Amazon S3, AWS, buckets and data connections to help create a centralized data structure and make data usable for other departments by adapting to new data systems and problem solving to make it readable
- Collaborated with a cross-functional team to help create and troubleshoot a Ticket Exchange App for customers
- Trusted to learn an in depth understanding of Looker in order to advise the team on its uses for the company

#### Oakland County, Parks Attendant

Leonard, MI -- June 2017 - August 2018

- Collected payments from clients and compiled cash transaction reports; Audited cash overages/shortages
- Daily customer engagement when communicating with others to supervise park activities and private parties

#### **Programming Languages and Software**

Python, R, C++, MatLab, SQL, HTML5, CSS, Advanced Excel, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Looker-, JavaScript

#### **Leadership and Projects**

University of Michigan Sports Analytics Class, Sports Analytics Society

- · Meet with the Dean of the School of Information once a week to discuss my work as a Sports Scientists for the University of Michigan Softball team
- · Attend weekly student lead meetings to discuss the innovation of the analytical effect on the sporting events

# **University of Michigan Women in Science** and Engineering Program

·Attended classes bi-weekly to discuss with other minorities in their programs, progress and strategies for success

## **Lapeer High School OMNI Leadership Council Vice President, NHS Treasurer**

· Planned Service projects for students to engage with the community

Lapeer High School Outstanding Senior Award, Varsity Softball and Basketball Team Captain